Guide to the Hal Lehrman papers, 1940-1970.
Lehrman, Hal papers
- Country Subject File Collection
  - Morocco - Economy (Box 28, Folder 427)
  - Morocco - France (Box 28, Folder 428)
  - Morocco - Foreign (Box 28, Folder 429)
  - Morocco - Mauritania (Box 28, Folder 430)
  - Morocco - Middle East (Box 28, Folder 431)
  - Morocco - North Africa (Box 28, Folder 432)
  - Morocco - Politics, 1956 and after (Box 28, Folder 433)
  - Morocco - Politics, Through 1955 (Box 28, Folder 434)
  - Morocco - Soviet (Box 28, Folder 435)
  - Morocco - Spain (Box 28, Folder 436)
  - Morocco - U.S. (Box 28, Folder 437)
  - Nigeria (Box 28, Folder 438)
  - North Africa - Background (Box 28, Folder 439)
  - North Africa - Bibliography (Box 28, Folder 440)
  - North Africa - Economy (Box 28, Folder 441)
  - North Africa - Politics (Box 28, Folder 442)
  - North Africa - West (Box 29, Folder 443)
  - Norway (Box 29, Folder 444)
  - Oil, 1958 and after (Box 29, Folder 445)
  - Oil, 1945-1957 (Box 29, Folder 446)
  - Pakistan, 1965 and after (Box 29, Folder 447)
  - Pakistan, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 448)
  - Palestinians (Box 29, Folder 449)
  - Poland (Box 29, Folder 450)
  - Poland - Background (Box 29, Folder 451)
  - Poland - Economy, 1940-1950 (Box 29, Folder 452)
  - Poland - Foreign, 1940-1946 (Box 29, Folder 453)
  - Poland - Political, 1940-1950 (Box 29, Folder 454)
  - Portugal (Box 29, Folder 455)
  - Rhodesia (Box 29, Folder 456)
  - Romania (Box 30, Folder 457)
  - Romania- Unfiled (Box 30, Folder 458)
  - Romania- Unfiled, 1947-1948 (Box 30, Folder 459)
  - Romania- Economy, 1948-1949 (Box 30, Folder 460)
  - Romania- Politics, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 461)
  - Rwanda (Box 30, Folder 462)
  - Satellites (Box 30, Folder 463)
  - Saudi Arabia - Background (Box 30, Folder 464)
  - Saudi Arabia - Chronological (Box 30, Folder 465)
  - Saudi Arabia - Economy (Box 30, Folder 466)
  - Saudi Arabia - Foreign (Box 30, Folder 467)
  - Saudi Arabia - Middle East (Box 30, Folder 468)
  - Saudi Arabia - Political (Box 30, Folder 469)
  - Saudi Arabia - Syria (Box 30, Folder 470)
  - Saudi Arabia - U.S. (Box 30, Folder 471)
  - Scandinavia (Box 30, Folder 472)
  - Senegal (Box 30, Folder 473)
  - Sierra-Leon (Box 30, Folder 474)
  - Somali (Box 30, Folder 475)
  - South Africa (Box 30, Folder 476)
  - Soviet - Asia (Box 30, Folder 477)
  - Soviet - Background (Box 30, Folder 478)
  - Soviet - Bibliography, Biography (Box 30, Folder 479)
  - Soviet - China (Box 30, Folder 480)
  - Soviet - Egypt (Box 31, Folder 481)
  - Soviet - Economy (Box 31, Folder 482)
  - Soviet - Japan (Box 31, Folder 483)
  - Soviet - Middle East (Box 31, Folder 484)
  - Soviet - Military (Box 31, Folder 485)
  - Soviet - Politics, 1970 and after (Box 31, Folder 486)
  - Soviet - Politics (Box 31, Folder 487)
  - Soviet - Satellites (Box 31, Folder 488)
  - Soviet - Vietnam (Box 31, Folder 489)
  - Spain (Box 31, Folder 490)
  - Sudan (Box 31, Folder 491)
  - Sweden (Box 31, Folder 492)
  - Syria - Background (Box 31, Folder 493)
  - Syria - Biography (Box 31, Folder 494)
  - Syria - Britain (Box 31, Folder 495)
  - Syria - Germany (Box 31, Folder 496)
  - Soviet Unfiled (Box 31, Folder 497)
  - Syria - Economy (Box 32, Folder 498)
  - Syria - Foreign - Economy (Box 32, Folder 499)
  - Syria - Foreign (Box 32, Folder 500)
  - Syria - France (Box 32, Folder 501)
  - Syria - Lebanon (Box 33, Folder 529)
  - Syria - Middle East (Box 32, Folder 502)
  - Syria - Political, 1964 and after (Box 32, Folder 503)
  - Syria - Political, To 1963 (Box 32, Folder 504)
  - Syria - Soviet, 1945 and after (Box 32, Folder 506)
  - Syria - Turkey (Box 32, Folder 507)
  - Syria - U.S., 1957 and after (Box 32, Folder 508)
  - Syria - U.S., 1945-1956 (Box 32, Folder 509)
  - Tanzania (Box 32, Folder 510)
  - Thailand (Box 33, Folder 536)
  - Tunisia - Africa (Box 32, Folder 511)
  - Tunisia - Background (Box 32, Folder 512)
  - Tunisia - Biography (Box 32, Folder 513)
  - Tunisia - Britain (Box 33, Folder 534)
  - Tunisia - China (Box 33, Folder 535)
  - Tunisia - Economy (Box 32, Folder 514)
  - Tunisia - Foreign (Box 33, Folder 531)
  - Tunisia - France - Economy (Box 33, Folder 532)
  - Tunisia - France- Political (Box 32, Folder 515)
  - Tunisia - Middle East (Box 32, Folder 516)
  - Tunisia - Political (Box 32, Folder 517)
  - Tunisia - Soviet Union (Box 33, Folder 533)
  - Tunisia - U.S. - Economy (Box 32, Folder 518)
  - Tunisia - U.S. - Political (Box 32, Folder 519)
  - Turkey - Background (Box 32, Folder 520)
  - Turkey - Background (Box 32, Folder 521)
  - Turkey - Biography (Box 32, Folder 522)
  - Turkey - Economy (Box 32, Folder 523)
  - Turkey - Foreign (Box 33, Folder 530)
  - Turkey - Greece (Box 33, Folder 524)
  - Turkey - Political, 1940-1950 (Box 33, Folder 525)
  - Turkey - Political (Box 33, Folder 526)
  - Turkey - Soviet (Box 33, Folder 527)
  - Turkey - U.S. (Box 33, Folder 528)
  - Uganda (Box 33, Folder 537)
  - U.N. (Box 33, Folder 538)
  - Vietnam, 1969 and after (Box 33, Folder 539)
  - Vietnam, Through 1968 (Box 33, Folder 540)
  - West, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 541)
  - West, 1964 and after (Box 33, Folder 542)
  - West, To 1962 (Box 34, Folder 543)
  - West - Africa (Box 34, Folder 544)
  - West - Algeria (Box 34, Folder 545)
  - West - Asia, 1968 and after (Box 34, Folder 546)
  - West - Asia, To 1968 (Box 34, Folder 547)
  - West - Bibliography (Box 34, Folder 548)
  - West - Cambodia (Box 34, Folder 549)
  - West - China (Box 34, Folder 550)
  - West - Cuba (Box 34, Folder 551)
  - West - Congo (Box 34, Folder 552)
  - West - Cyprus (Box 34, Folder 553)
  - West - Economy (Box 35, Folder 554)
  - West - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 555)
  - West - Foreign (Box 35, Folder 556)
  - West - Germany (Box 35, Folder 557)
  - West - Greece (Box 35, Folder 558)
  - West - Israel (Box 35, Folder 559)
  - West - Laos (Box 35, Folder 560)
  - West - Latin America (Box 35, Folder 561)
  - West - Middle East, 1960-1968 (Box 35, Folder 562)
  - West - Middle East, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 563)
  - West - Malaysia (Box 35, Folder 564)
  - West -Middle East, 1968 and after (Box 36, Folder 565)
  - West - Middle East, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 566)
  - West -Middle East, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 567)
  - West - Middle East, 1943-1955 (Box 36, Folder 568)
  - West - Military (Box 36, Folder 569)
  - West - Nato (Box 36, Folder 570)
  - West - North Africa (Box 36, Folder 571)
  - "A War Atlas For Americans" Book, 1944 (Box 36)
  - West - Political (Box 37, Folder 572)
  - West - Press (Box 37, Folder 573)
  - West - Press - Africa (Box 37, Folder 574)
  - West - Press - Algeria (Box 37, Folder 575)
  - West - Press - Asia (Box 37, Folder 576)
  - West - Press - China (Box 37, Folder 577)
  - West - Press - Cuba (Box 37, Folder 578)
  - West - Press - Dominican (Box 37, Folder 579)
  - West - Press - Economy (Box 37, Folder 580)
  - West - Press - Egypt (Box 37, Folder 581)
  - West - Press - Foreign (Box 37, Folder 582)
  - West - Press - France - Repatries (Box 37, Folder 583)
  - West - Press - France (Box 37, Folder 584)
  - West - Press - France (Box 37, Folder 585)
  - West - Press - Greece (Box 37, Folder 586)
  - West - Press - Indonesia (Box 37, Folder 587)
  - West - Press - Israel (Box 37, Folder 588)
  - West - Press - Japan (Box 37, Folder 589)
  - West - Press - Jews (Box 37, Folder 590)
  - West - Press - Latam (Box 37, Folder 591)
  - West - Press - Israel (Box 37, Folder 592)
  - West - Press - Military (Box 37, Folder 593)
  - West - Press - Middle East (Box 37, Folder 594)
  - West - Press - Middle East, 1969 and after (Box 37, Folder 595)
  - West - Press - Political (Box 38, Folder 596)
  - West - Press - Pakistan (Box 38, Folder 597)
  - West - Press - Nato (Box 38, Folder 598)
  - West - Press - Satellite (Box 38, Folder 599)
  - West - Press - Satellite - Military (Box 38, Folder 600)
  - West - Press - Soviet (Box 38, Folder 601)
  - West - Press - U.N. (Box 38, Folder 602)
  - West - Press - Vietnam, February 1968 and after (Box 38, Folder 603)
  - West - Press - Vietnam, January 1967 to February 1968 (Box 38, Folder 604)
  - West - Press - Vietnam, August 1966 to December 1966 (Box 38, Folder 605)
  - West - Press - Vietnam, January 1966 to July 1966 (Box 38, Folder 606)
  - West - Press - Vietnam, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 607)
  - West - Satellite - Economy (Box 39, Folder 608)
  - West - Satellite - Political, 1966 and after (Box 39, Folder 609)
  - West - Satellite - Political, To 1966 (Box 39, Folder 610)
  - West - Soviet (Box 39, Folder 611)
  - West - Soviet - Economy (Box 39, Folder 612)
  - West - Soviet - Military (Box 39, Folder 613)
  - West - Soviet - Political, 1970 and after (Box 39, Folder 614)
  - West - Soviet - Political, 1965-1969 (Box 39, Folder 615)
  - West - Soviet - Political, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 616)
  - West - Soviet - Political, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 617)
  - West (Box 40, Folder 618)
  - West - Turkey (Box 32, Folder 505)
  - West - U.N. (Box 40, Folder 619)
  - West - Vietnam, 1970 and after (Box 40, Folder 620 A)
  - West - Vietnam, 1970 and after (Box 40, Folder 620 B)
  - West - Vietnam, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 621)
  - West - Vietnam, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 622)
  - West - Vietnam, October 1966 to December 1966 (Box 41, Folder 623)
  - West - Vietnam, March 1966 to September 1966 (Box 41, Folder 624)
  - West - Vietnam, January 1966 to February 1966 (Box 41, Folder 625)
  - West - Vietnam, June 1965 to December 1965 (Box 41, Folder 626)
  - West - Vietnam, January 1965 to May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 627)
  - West - Vietnam, August 1964 to December 1964 (Box 41, Folder 628)
  - West - Vietnam, January 1964 to July 1964 (Box 41, Folder 629)
  - West - Vietnam, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 630)
  - Yemen - Background (Box 42, Folder 631)
  - Yemen - Middle East (Box 42, Folder 632)
  - Yemen - Political (Box 42, Folder 633)
  - Yemen - Soviet (Box 42, Folder 634)
  - Yemen - U.N. (Box 42, Folder 635)
  - Yemen - U.S. (Box 42, Folder 636)
  - Yugoslavia - Temp. (Box 42, Folder 637)
  - Yugoslavia - Background (Box 42, Folder 638)
  - Yugoslavia - Unfiled, 1947-1948 (Box 42, Folder 639)
  - Yugoslavia - Economic (Box 42, Folder 640)
  - Yugoslavia - Political (Box 42, Folder 641)
  - Yugoslavia, 1950 and after (Box 42, Folder 642)
  - Zambia (Box 42, Folder 643)
- Overseas Press Club
  - Publications, 1965-1970 (Box 42, Folder 644)
  - Overseas Press Club (Box 42, Folder 645)
  - Overseas Press Club (Box 42, Folder 646)
  - Publications, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 647)
  - Overseas Press Club (Box 43, Folder 648)
  - Bulletins (Box 43, Folder 649 A)
  - Bulletins (Box 43, Folder 649 B)
  - Overseas Press Club (Box 43, Folder 650)
  - Memos (Box 43, Folder 651)
  - Overseas Press Club (Box 43, Folder 652)
  - Overseas Press Club (Box 43, Folder 653)
  - Correspondences (Box 44, Folder 654)
  - Overseas Press Club, 1960-1966 (Box 44, Folder 655)
  - Overseas Press Club (Box 44, Folder 656)
  - Housing (Box 44, Folder 657)
  - Insurance (Box 44, Folder 658)
  - International (Box 44, Folder 659)
  - Lecture Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 660)
  - Long-Range Planning, 1967-1970 (Box 44, Folder 661)
  - Membership (Box 44, Folder 662)
  - Memorial (Box 44, Folder 663)
  - Memorial - St. Bride's, London (Box 44, Folder 664)
  - Memorial Wall, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 665)
  - Misc., 1967-1969 (Box 44, Folder 666)
  - Murrow Forum, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 667)
  - Murrow Forum, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 668)
  - Murrow Forum, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 669)
  - Music (Box 44, Folder 670)
  - National Press Club (Box 44, Folder 671)
  - Nominating Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 44, Folder 672)
  - Overseas Recruitment, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 673)
  - Misc. (Box 44, Folder 674)
  - Hal Lehrman Personal (Box 44, Folder 675)
  - Hal Lehrman Personal and Undated Material, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 676)
  - Hal Lehrman Personal, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 677)
  - Hal Lehrman Personal, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 678)
  - Photographic Communication, 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 679)
  - Placement, 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 680)
  - Post-Agnew Panel (Box 45, Folder 681)
  - Premier (Box 45, Folder 682)
  - President's Committee (Box 45, Folder 683)
  - Press Relations, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 684)
  - Printers (Box 45, Folder 685)
  - Program Council, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 686)
  - Program Council, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 687)
  - Program Council, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 688)
  - Public Information Council, 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 689)
  - Radio/TV, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 690)
  - Who's Who (Box 45, Folder 691)
  - Yacht Club (Box 45, Folder 692)
  - Reception Committee (Box 45, Folder 693)
  - Reciprocal Arrangements, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 694)
  - Regional Dinners, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 695)
  - Rentals (Box 45, Folder 696)
  - Reunion Committee (Box 45, Folder 697)
  - Root, Lin - Secretary (Box 45, Folder 698)
  - Sheldon, James H. - Treasurer (Box 45, Folder 699)
  - Special Planning (Box 45, Folder 700)
  - Sponsors Committee (Box 45, Folder 701)
  - Stamp (Box 45, Folder 702)
  - Students, 1968-1970 (Box 45, Folder 703)
  - Tenants (Box 45, Folder 704)
  - Travel, 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 705)
  - Uneso, 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 706)
  - Union (Box 45, Folder 707)
  - U.N. Silver Jubilee (Box 45, Folder 708)
  - Washington, 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 709)
  - Welcome Home kit (Box 45, Folder 710)
  - Admissions/Membership, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 711)
  - Admissions/Membership, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 712)
  - Annual Awards, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 713)
  - Art, 1967-1970 (Box 45, Folder 714)
  - Market (Box 46, Folder 715)
  - Annual Awards Dinner, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 716)
  - Annual Awards Dinner, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 717)
  - Annual Awards Dinner, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 718)
  - Annual Awards Dinner, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 719)
  - Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 720)
  - Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 721)
  - ANPA, 1965-1969 (Box 46, Folder 722)
  - Archives (Box 46, Folder 723)
  - Army and Navy Club (Box 46, Folder 724)
  - Awards, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 725)
  - Awards, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 726)
  - Banquet (Box 46, Folder 727)
  - Bistro (Box 46, Folder 728)
  - Board of Governors, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 729)
  - Board of Governors - Special Meeting, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 730)
  - Board of Governors - General, 1967-1969 (Box 46, Folder 731)
  - Bolshevik Revolution, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 732)
  - Bond Proposal (Box 46, Folder 733)
  - Book Night, 1967-1970 (Box 46, Folder 734)
  - Book Publishing, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 735)
  - Building, 1966-1970 (Box 46, Folder 736)
  - Bulletin, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 737)
  - Bulletin (Box 46, Folder 738)
  - Bulletin, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 739)
  - Bulletin, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 740)
  - Bulletin, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 742)
  - Chapters, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 742)
  - Certificate of Incorporation - OPC (Box 46, Folder 743)
  - Committees General, 1967-1969 (Box 46, Folder 744)
  - Constitution, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 745)
  - Correspondents Fund, July 1969 to December 1969 (Box 46, Folder 746)
  - Correspondents Fund, January 1969 to June 1969 (Box 46, Folder 747)
  - Correspondents Fund, 1953-1968 (Box 46, Folder 748)
  - Credit, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 749)
  - Dateline (Box 47, Folder 750)
  - Eban (Box 47, Folder 751)
  - Elections, 1967-1970 (Box 47, Folder 752)
  - Electronics Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 753)
  - Entertainment Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 754)
  - Financial, 1967-1969 (Box 47, Folder 755)
  - Film Committee (Box 47, Folder 756)
  - Food and Beverage, 1968-1970 (Box 47, Folder 757)
  - Foreign Press Clubs (Box 47, Folder 758)
  - Freedom of the Press, 1967-1970 (Box 47, Folder 759)
  - Graphic Arts (Box 47, Folder 760)
  - Hershey, Burnet (Box 47, Folder 761)
  - Homecoming, 1967-1969 (Box 47, Folder 762)
  - House, 1969-1970 (Box 47, Folder 763)
  - Foundation Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 47, Folder 764)
  - Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 765)
  - OPC Unsorted Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 766)